I bought two expensive dictionaries here half an hour ago,
半小时前我在这里买了两本很贵的辞典,
but I forgot to take them with me.
但是我忘了带走他们.
Who served you, sir?
是谁服务您的,先生?
The lady who is standing behind the counter.
站在柜台后面的那位女士.
Which books did you buy?
您买的是两本什么书?
The books which are on the counter.
就是柜台上的那两本.
Did you serve this gentleman half an hour ago, Caroline?
Caroline,半小时前你服务过这位先生吗?
He says he's the man who bought these books.
他说他就是买这两本书的人.
I can't remember.
我记不起来了.
The man who I served was wearing a hat.
我服务的那个人戴着一顶帽子.
Have you got a hat, sir? Yes, I have.
先生,您有帽子吗?有的,我有帽子.
Would you put it on, please?
请您把帽子戴上好吗?
All right.
好吧.
Is this the man that you served, Caroline?
Caroline,这就是你接服务的那个人吗?
Yes.I recognize him now.
是他.我现在认出他来了.